<resources>
    <string name="app_name">About Me</string>
    <string name="name">Emily Ava</string>
    <string name="yellow_star">Yellow star</string>
    <string name="bio">Hello, my name is Emily.
    \n\n\t I am a senior CS student at Troy University. \n
        I am learning how to develop Android applications, and I am enjoying it a lot.
        I am currently looking for jobs in Huntsville, AL. \n
        My preferences are in the fields of app development, software engineering, and cyber security. \n\n
        \t My hobbies include gaming, cars, reading, watching shows and taking naps. \n
        My favorite games are the Elder Scrolls series, the Witcher series, and Pokemon. \n
        My favorite book is Memoirs of a Geisha by Arthur Golden. \n
        My favorite shows are Game of Thrones, Vikings, Good Trouble and Jane the Virgin. \n\n
        \t I have a very strong interest in cars, and would like to build my own one day to drift in competitions. \n
        My favorite car is a Nissan r34, and I would have it painted dark purple with white wheels. \n
        I love to watch Ken Block\'s Gymkhana videos. \n
        Another thing I enjoy is watching YouTube videos. My favorite YouTubers are PewDiePie, Safiya Nygaard,
        Jenna Marbles, Linzor, CollisCool, and Andrea Russet.\n\n
        \t Food is another one of my passions. I am not a picky eater and will eat almost anything -
        besides ketchup, mushrooms, or iced tea. \n
        My favorite food is sushi, and I love to go to Chow King in Dothan, AL to eat as much as I want. \n
        I also love burgers, kimchi, and ddeokboki, which is a Korean street food dish consisting
        of chewy rice cake in a spicy red sauce. \n
        I love traveling as well; one of my favorite things about it is trying different ethnicity\'s foods.\n
        I have been to Greece, Turkey and Israel. My favorite food  out of those was in Greece.
        They had a dish called mousakka which was like a cheesier,
        heartier version of American lasagna.\n\n
    </string>
</resources>
